<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Welcome! on Sri harsha Maddirala</title>
    <link>https://sri-harsha99.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Welcome! on Sri harsha Maddirala</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 20:06:33 +0530</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sri-harsha99.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Price Tracking with notification</title>
      <link>https://sri-harsha99.github.io/post/chapter-5/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 11 Aug 2020 20:06:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sri-harsha99.github.io/post/chapter-5/</guid>
      <description>Well, this is August 2020, Six months into the COVID-19 lockdown and I want to play rocket league. I don&amp;rsquo;t have any controller, So I went to Amazon and Flipkart to check the price. Because of COVID global supply chain has been messed up and prices went up due to limited stock. An Xbox controller which usually sells for ₹3500 he&amp;rsquo;s currently selling for ₹5500. I can buy it but I&amp;rsquo;m the kind of person who is satisfied with the purchase only if I bought it on sale.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Floyd&#39;s Hare and Tortoise</title>
      <link>https://sri-harsha99.github.io/post/chapter-4/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 01 Jul 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sri-harsha99.github.io/post/chapter-4/</guid>
      <description>Two weeks before, I have been asked to find duplicate number in an array where numbers in an array belong to [0,sizeofarray-1] in an interview. Method I used is to sort the array and check each number with previous number in the array. If both are equal, then that is the duplicate number. This method uses O(nlogn) time complexity because of time complexity. Interview didn&amp;rsquo;t go well. Later, I came across this question in leetcode and found that there is another approach that can be done in O(n) time complexity.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Generative adverserial networks</title>
      <link>https://sri-harsha99.github.io/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sri-harsha99.github.io/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Above images are computer generated based on celebA dataset by using GAN. This has been generated by Tero Karras at Nvidia. Published Paper.
In this article, we will use GAN, a network of Generator and Discriminator to generate facial images by using Tensorflow 2.0 and Keras libraries. Dataset used for generation of images is Faces94. Link to dataset. This article is adapted from Tensorflow GAN documentation.
First, we load necessary libraries and dataset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curating News with NLP</title>
      <link>https://sri-harsha99.github.io/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sri-harsha99.github.io/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>In this Information retrieval project, we used web scrapping and basic IR techniques to see how a particular news is portrayed by different news paper mediums. link to Repo
We selected BBC, Hindustan Times and Times of India and did scrapping. Code for scrapping is [name of paper].py in the repo. SQL files with name as news papers will simply put data from py code into SQL server. We used Django framework to integrate backend and frontend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One-hot encoding</title>
      <link>https://sri-harsha99.github.io/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sri-harsha99.github.io/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will discuss why one-hot encoding is needed and how it is done using different libraries.
What is one-hot encoding? In practical terms, it is to convert categorical data into into a form by which learning model can improve it&amp;rsquo;s accuracy.   In the above picture, there are three categories of food. After, we one-hot encode this data, each category gets it&amp;rsquo;s own column and that column represents, data present in the row, belongs to that category or not.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Simulated Annealing</title>
      <link>https://sri-harsha99.github.io/post/chapter-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 14 May 2020 15:40:49 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sri-harsha99.github.io/post/chapter-7/</guid>
      <description>Simulated Annealing can be used to find global optima when there are man local optima.
  Initially, the temperature parameter in the function is set to a high value and it keeps on decreasing until it is zero. When it is high, algorithm takes a risk in choosing a sub-optimal path with the goal of reaching global optima. This behaviour decreases as tempeareture decreases. There is also a probability factor that is directly proportional to the temperature parameter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://sri-harsha99.github.io/contact/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sri-harsha99.github.io/contact/</guid>
      <description> Your Name Email Address An email address is required.  Message   </description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>