<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Articles on Sri harsha Maddirala</title>
    <link>https://example.com/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Articles on Sri harsha Maddirala</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Mar 2017 12:00:00 -0500</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="https://example.com/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Generative adverserial networks</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/chapter-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 20 Jun 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/chapter-1/</guid>
      <description>Above images are computer generated based on celebA dataset by using GAN. This has been generated by Tero Karras at Nvidia. Published Paper.
In this article, we will use GAN, a network of Generator and Discriminator to generate facial images by using Tensorflow 2.0 and Keras libraries. Dataset used for generation of images is Faces94. Link to dataset. This article is adapted from Tensorflow GAN documentation.
First, we load necessary libraries and dataset.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Curating News with NLP</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/chapter-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 17 Jun 2020 11:13:32 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/chapter-3/</guid>
      <description>In this Information retrieval project, we used web scrapping and basic IR techniques to see how a particular news is portrayed by different news paper mediums. link to Repo
We selected BBC, Hindustan Times and Times of India and did scrapping. Code for scrapping is [name of paper].py in the repo. SQL files with name as news papers will simply put data from py code into SQL server. We used Django framework to integrate backend and frontend.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>One-hot encoding</title>
      <link>https://example.com/post/chapter-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 10 Jun 2020 11:00:59 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://example.com/post/chapter-2/</guid>
      <description>In this article, we will discuss why one-hot encoding is needed and how it is done using different libraries.
What is one-hot encoding? In practical terms, it is to convert categorical data into into a form by which learning model can improve it&amp;rsquo;s accuracy.   In the above picture, there are three categories of food. After, we one-hot encode this data, each category gets it&amp;rsquo;s own column and that column represents, data present in the row, belongs to that category or not.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>